let's also talk about some more ideas
where we get you a few ideas of profit
from our colleagues at money control pro
nehad away joins in to talk about a
stock that she's been tracking closely
today we are going to talk about isis
lumbar general insurance the insurer
faced multiple challenges in the year
gone by the claims ratio increased in
the first half of the fiscal due to long
reporting pail of health claims the
motor insurance segment which is the
largest uh faced continuous headwind
because of heightened competition chip
shortages in the four-wheeler segment
and weak demand the tubular segment the
merger with bharti extra also got
reflected in effect 22 and weighed down
the financials uh despite these issues
uh the insurer managed to report profit
in fi 22 as underwriting loss was offset
by higher investment income however
things are said to improve going forward
health insurance has emerged as the
fastest growing segment caused the
pandemic due to increased awareness and
shift in customers attitude towards
protection buying uh the motor insurance
is also set for revival in fi 23. the
high in third party motor tariff rates
uh by the regulator after no revision
for the two consecutive years is
positive for the company uh the
operating uh synergies and the cost
savings from the merger will also get
reflected in fi 23. the stock has
corrected more than 30 from its 52-week
high price in terms of valuation uh the
company is trading at around six times
fi 22 book value which undoubtedly is
rich however i say say loan but premium
valuation will sustain uh given its
market leading share in structural goods
sector fairly diversified product mix
it's a strong multi-channel distribution
network and healthy profitability and
solvency profile uh the current weakness
in the stock price should be utilized to
add this stock
neha thank you so much for joining us
with all those details with that we'll
slip into a short break now and as we do
that here's something for our viewers
money control pro is celebrating its
third anniversary with special offers
get a money control pro subscription at
just 365 rupees for one year and a whale
of offers worth more than one lakh
rupees
[Music]